Guide to the Ta-Chun Hsu papers 14362723
C. V. Starr East Asian Library
- Series III: Printed materials, 印刷品, 1930-2006
  - Books, magazines, and articles, 書冊類, 1930-2006
    - 唐狄梁公碑 /Tang Di Liang gong bei. By 趙孟頫書; 范仲淹撰; Mengfu Zhao; Zhongyan Fan, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 张元济诗文 /Zhang yuan ji shi wen. By yuan ji Zhang, 张元济, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 我的父亲张元济 /Wo de fu qin Zhang Yuanji. By 张树年, Shunian Zhang, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 張元濟書札 /Zhang Yuanji shuzha. Publisher: 商務印書館, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 丁文江這個人 /Ding wen jiang zhe ge ren. By Hu Shih et al. 胡適等著, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Part of 傳記文學叢書之二十一
    - 紐約客談 /Niuyue ke tan. By 喬志高著 George Kao, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 約園著作選輯 / Yueyuan zhuzuo xuanji. By Shouyong Zhang; Zhilian Zhang, 張壽鏞著. 張芝聯編., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 中國中古思想小史 /Zhongguo zhong gu si xiang xiao shi. By Hu Shih, 胡適, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Dai lin ji / 待麟集: Chinese character text of Waiting for the unicorn: poems and lyrics of China's last dynasty, 1644-1911. Edited by Irving Yucheng Lo and William Schultz, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Yuen Ren Chao's autobiography: first 30 years, from 1892-1921. By Yuen Ren Chao, 趙元任, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Only Volume II
    - 八十年、五十年回憶 /Ba shi nian, wu shi nian hui yi. By 楊步偉, 趙元任; Buwei Yang Chao; Yuen Ren Chao, circa 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 一個女人的自傳 /Yi ge nü ren de zi zhuan. By Buwei Yang, 楊步偉著, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 師門五年記 /Shi men wu nian ji. By Ergang Luo; Erh-kang Lo 羅爾綱撰, 1958; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 5)
      第一版, 1958. 適之再校本(民47,十二, 二十八, 夜).
    - 蔣百里先生百年誕辰紀念冊 / Jiang bai li xian sheng bai nian dan chen ji nian ce, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
      With photograph of Frances L. Chu, 1999 July 29
    - The Hiss case: a lesson for American people, 1959; 2 copies (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Speech of Hon. Richard M. Nixon of California in the House of Representatives. Thursday, January 26, 1950. Inscribed to T.C. Hsu from Hu Shih
    - Eleven Centuries of Chinese Printing, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Exhibition of books from the Gest Oriental Library at Princeton University Library, February 20-April 20, 1952. Curated by Hu Shih
    - United Nations at the Crossroads, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Address by Liu Chieh, Chairman of the Delegation of the Republic of China to the Twentieth Session of the General Assembly of the United Nations
    - Communist China, fact and myth. By Chʻun-ming Chang, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Publisher: [Place of publication not identified] [1956]. Series: The new leader, sect. 2, Sept. 24, 1956
    - 大陸三年 / Da lu san nian. By 靈子, pseud. Lingzi, pseud., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 大成 / Da cheng: issue 33, 1976 August 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 大人 / Da ren: issue 27, 1972 July 15 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Zhuan ji wen xue = 傳記文學 = Biographical literature
      - Vol.4, no.5, 1964 May (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Vol.17, no.5 (issue 102), 1970 November (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Vol.28, no.5 (issue 168), 1976 May (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 海外論壇 = World forum = Hai wai lun tan., 1961-1962; 4 items (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Vol.2, no.7-8, 11-12; Vol.3, no.5.
    - 美哉中華 = Beautiful China, a pictorial monthly, 1970 November (Box 9, Folder 1)